PAUL GREENFIELD

London, SE18 5NH

Telephone: 07900 213270 Email: percyg@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced IT support technician with a background in web, desktop and database development. An in-depth knowledge of building, deploying and troubleshooting hardware and software. With an attention to detail and an eye to streamlining tasks with the ability to develop custom software. Excellent client facing skills and a responsible team worker, while being able to work on my own initiative when necessary.

KEY SKILLS

- 20 years' client facing office IT hardware and software support.
- 15 years' experience developing and deploying full stack web applications.
- Highly motivated and dedicated professional seeking to leverage my extensive experience in client-facing IT hardware and software support, as well as my expertise in developing and deploying full stack web applications, while remaining eager to embrace and master new languages and technologies in the ever-evolving tech landscape.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer – School of Code March 2023 – July 2023

- **Problem Solving:** Routinely practicing breaking down problems into small manageable pieces of information. Collaborating with others to obtain different perspectives to find effective solutions.
- **Pair programming:** Liaised with a new partner every day in navigator/driver to solve problems and share knowledge.
- **Teamwork:** Operated in a team of 6 using the agile methodologies via sprints, planning on Trello, daily stand-ups and retros to create and deploy a full stack application
- **Planning:** Incorporating git merging strategies to avoid git conflicts. Detailed assessment and breakdown of the problem into Trello tickets to ensure clarity and direction for the team.
- **Growth Mindset:** Exposed to new tech stacks and frameworks continuously and applied them using daily workshops, hackathons and team full stack projects.

Camden City Islington and Westminster Bereavement Service IT Consultant & Software Engineer October 2015 – Present

- Sole software developer for in-house custom client / counsellor management software, written using ASP.NET from legacy Classic ASP, CSS, JavaScript and SQL Server. Maintained on Server 2016 with IIS 10 and SQL Server with email provided by on premises Exchange Server 2016. Features include:
 - Secure client and counsellor SQL server database written in VB.net for remote access.
 - \circ Custom server Windows Form applications for sending email and SMS appointment reminders.
 - o quarterly statistic reports as required by the local authority.
- Installation of network shares, user accounts and printer/scanner sharing & Active Directory.
- Support of Office, antivirus software, BitLocker and 3rd party encryption. Ongoing desktop support for Windows 10 when needed.

HCL Technologies

AVI Technician January 2020 - November 2020

Part of the London VIO team in house at Facebook responsible for inspecting and maintaining all the video conferencing equipment across all three Facebook sites.

- Hardware and software maintenance on video and audio conference equipment.
- Troubleshooting conference Apps such as Webex, Zoom, Blue Jeans.
- Installation and configuration of video and audio conference equipment.
- Supporting and troubleshooting Cisco AV/VC devices, MX Series, Crestron, LCDs, and Projectors.
- Work with Client, Engineers and different layers to troubleshoot and solve problems.
- Communicate effectively with clients to identify needs and evaluate solutions.
- Daily preventive maintenance and inspections of AV/VC equipment.
- Operations validation against documented VC standards.

Freelance IT Support & Web Developer July 2004 - October 2015

- Created website http://www.totemrecords.com using ASP / SQL Server 7 / VBScript.
 A full e-commerce solution including content management system, user search by keyword/genre/format and an editable shopping basket.
- Hardware and software support for Martin Leach Publishers, Vortex Bookshop, Wilton Films and other private clients.
- Web development for official PlayStation web site and creating various other ecommerce websites.

www.whatsonwhen.com

Web Developer & IT Support July 2000 - June 2002

- Site development with ASP/VBScript/SQL Server 7
- Hardware / software installation and office IT support and troubleshooting
- Sole Development of the mobile phone version of the site
- Server admin (Windows 2000 / IIS / Linux)

School of Oriental and African Studies (SOAS)

IT Support September 1999 - March 2000

- Troubleshooting staff IT problems
- Installing and setting up new equipment and software
- Auditing school computer system
- Updating intranet web site with latest information and Y2K patches

INTERESTS:

Lower power microcontroller projects for automation and robotics. Building/overclocking custom water-cooled gaming PCs. Performing and recording music.

EDUCATION:

Web Development with ASP.NET & Programming with C#, London Academy of IT.

Web Development, NVQII & NVQIII. MicroTech, Great Guildford St, London, SE1. HTML, VB Script, SQL and ASP training.

Diploma in Sound Engineering, SAE Institute, London

A Levels in Pure & Applied Mathematics, Computer Science at North East Surrey College of Technology, Reigate Rd, Ewell, Surrey

O Levels in Mathematics, Physics, English Language, Computer Studies and History, Epsom High School, Epsom, Surrey

DRIVING LICENSE Full UK

REFERENCES Available on request